zojirushi.com 2019-07-08

# Privacy Policy | zojirushi.com

**Privacy Statement**

Zojirushi America Corporation, its parent corporation, Zojirushi Corporation, and our respective subsidiaries (collectively "Zojirushi America Corporation") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. Zojirushi America Corporation shall comply with any Personal Data Protection Laws and other laws and strive to protect personal data under the following policy. The provisions of all such laws are incorporated herein by this reference. We provide this Privacy Statement to inform you of our Privacy Policy and practices.

By visiting us, you are accepting the practice described in this Privacy Policy. This policy applies to the website operated in the United States of America.

**Personal Information Defined:**

a. | Your first and last name;  
---|---  
b. | Your home or other physical address;  
c. | Your shipping address if different from above address;  
d. | Your E-mail address;  
e. | Your telephone or fax number;  
f. | Your credit card information;  
g. | Your product purchase history;  
h. | Any identifier that allows you to be contacted; and  
i. | Information concerning your visits to other websites that is used in combination with any of the above. This kind of information includes "click stream" information or information obtained from "cookies" such as information showing the last several websites that you visited and information about your profile or preferences. This information will not be "personally identifiable information" unless it is coupled with any of the information above, a-f.  
  
**What your Personal Information will be used for:**

If you choose to provide us with Personal Information about yourself, either through a form on our website or by sending us e-mail, we may collect and use that information to contact you or to send you additional information to process your purchase, provide service and support, and share product, service and company news and offerings with you.

We may be required to disclose Personal Information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, regulation, and other legal action or if we reasonably believe it is necessary to do so to protect our customers, the public, or us.

If you visit our website simply to browse, we may collect general information about the way in which you use our site, including the time and duration of visit, type of Web browser used, the operating system/platform you are using, your IP address, the websites from which you linked to us, and your CPU speed. We also may note whether and how you use the site by recording site traffic patterns and "clickstreams."

**How your Personal Information will be used:**

We will use your Personal Information to provide you with services and to help us better understand your needs and interests. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction or order, to communicate with you, to provide service and support, to update you on services and benefits, to personalize promotional offers and to personalize some of our websites. Occasionally we may also use your information to contact you for market research regarding our products or services. Sensitive Personal Information is collected only to facilitate our financial service providers' credit decisions and will be shared with them only with your permission.

Credit card information and sensitive personal data are not used for any other purpose by our financial services providers or us and will not be kept longer than necessary for providing the services, unless you ask us to retain your credit card information for future purchases. Credit card numbers are used only for processing payment and will not be used for any other purpose.

**Who else will be given your Personal Information:**

We do not sell, rent or lease any personally identifiable information you provide to any unrelated third party, but we may share it with related entities or with unrelated third parties in connection with our own marketing activities, your credit card processing, or the maintenance and operation of our site, or as may be legally required. (Please do not send confidential or sensitive information, to us through this site.)

**Our Security Precautions:**

We are committed to protecting the information you provide us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, we have in place appropriate physical and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

You are advised that other websites, which may be accessed through our site, may collect personally identifiable information about you. This privacy statement does not cover the information practices of those third-party web sites linked to us. Please contact them directly for their privacy statement.

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. SSL encryption is designed to make the information unreadable by anyone but us. This security measure is working when you see either the symbol of an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser) on the bottom of your browser window.

Although we use security that we believe to be appropriate to protect the personal identifying information disclosed to us on this website, we do not guarantee that our security precautions will protect against and we expressly disclaim any liability for any loss, misuse, or alteration of your Personal Information or from your access to or use of our information.

**Use of Cookies:**

New technologies are emerging on the Internet that help us deliver customized visitor experiences. We may use cookies to help us provide you with a fast, convenient shopping experience at our online store. A "cookie" is a data element a web site sends to your browser. It is stored on your computer and tells a website that a previous visitor has returned. It doesn't automatically give personal information about you, like your e-mail address or name. If you want to give us personal information through registration, then a cookie will help us deliver content based on your interests and preferences. Cookies help us monitor whether our website is functioning properly and helps us perform site traffic analysis.

**Changes to your Personal Information:**

If you do not want us to use your Personal Information to contact you, or if you wish to correct such information, please contact us at 800-733-6270 or e-mail

**Assets of the Corporation:**

If for any reason, our ownership changes or our assets sold, the customer list is a part of our asset pool and may be sold or transferred in accordance with any applicable laws without your consent.

**Changes to Policy Statement:**

If there are updates to the terms of our Privacy Statement, we will post those changes and update the revision date in this document, so you will always know what information we collect online, how we use it, and what choices you have.

**Children's Privacy (Age 12 and Under):**

Zojirushi America Corporation takes children's privacy seriously. We are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and we do not target our websites to children under 13.

We do not seek to collect Personal Information about children through our website. We do not condition a child's participation in an activity on the disclosure of more Personal Information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity.

If we become aware that a person submitting Personal Information to us through any part of our website is a child, we delete the information as soon as we discover it and do not use it for any purpose, nor do we disclose it to third parties.

Since we do not seek to collect any Personal Information about children, and we delete any information collected inadvertently as soon as we discover that a child has submitted it, we typically retain no information about children that could be reviewed or deleted. If a parent requests review or deletion of information about their child before we have discovered and deleted the information, then we will of course honor that request.
